Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
(Episode 13)
(الحلقة 13)
What era is this?
ما هو هذا العصر؟
Da Huan should have the right to choose.
ينبغي أن يكون لدى دا هوان الحق في الاختيار.
Yu Chen?
يو تشن؟
How could Yu Chen be a bad person?
كيف يمكن أن يكون يو تشن شخصًا سيئًا؟
Da Huan, are you happy being with me?
دا هوان، هل أنت سعيد بوجودك معي؟
What if she's longing to marry me?
ماذا لو كانت تتوق للزواج مني؟
Tong Sheng, you haven't been yourself lately.
تونغ شنغ، لم تكن نفسك في الآونة الأخيرة.
Tong Sheng, have you heard...
تونغ شنغ، هل سمعت...
about the merger and acquisition of our group?
حول اندماج واستحواذ مجموعتنا؟
I don't know what Chang Ming is thinking.
لا أعرف ماذا يفكر تشانج مينج.
He's willing to give up the pricing power.
إنه على استعداد للتخلي عن سلطة التسعير.
What?
ماذا؟
I remember what you said about the company's original purpose.
أتذكر ما قلته عن الغرض الأصلي للشركة.
It is to provide the public...
إن الهدف من ذلك هو توفير للجمهور...
with affordable and high-quality products.
مع منتجات بأسعار معقولة وعالية الجودة.
The products should be cost-effective.
ينبغي أن تكون المنتجات فعالة من حيث التكلفة.
But looking at how this is going,
ولكن بالنظر إلى كيفية سير الأمور،
the group is going to change strategies.
المجموعة سوف تغير استراتيجياتها.
Do you also think there's something wrong with this contract?
هل تعتقد أيضًا أن هناك خطأ في هذا العقد؟
I can't explain it either.
لا أستطيع أن أشرح ذلك أيضًا.
But something doesn't feel right.
لكن هناك شيء لا يبدو على ما يرام.
I can't put my finger on it.
لا أستطيع وضع إصبعي عليه.
Have you seen the contract?
هل رأيت العقد؟
No, I haven't.
لا، لم أفعل.
Besides, Chang Ming won't show it to me.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، تشانغ مينغ لن يظهر لي ذلك.
I see.
أرى.
I'll think of a way.
سأفكر في طريقة.
Okay, Tong Sheng. I'll get going then.
حسنًا، تونغ شينغ. سأذهب إذًا.
I just came to see you before I go out.
لقد أتيت فقط لرؤيتك قبل أن أخرج.
Jin Da Xi, let's switch identities tonight.
جين دا شي، دعنا نبدل الهويات الليلة.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm working overtime.
أنا أعمل لساعات إضافية.
It's so complicated.
إنه أمر معقد للغاية.
Xuebao Group?
مجموعة شيويباو؟
Yes. It's the merger and acquisition.
نعم، إنه الاندماج والاستحواذ.
I don't know why I'm so anxious.
لا أعلم لماذا أنا قلقة هكذا.
The contract has been signed.
تم توقيع العقد.
I'm still here researching.
لا أزال هنا أقوم بالبحث.
The contract has been filled out?
تم ملء العقد؟
We'll sign it at the press conference tomorrow.
سوف نوقع عليه في المؤتمر الصحفي غدا.
All the legal procedures are done.
تمت كافة الإجراءات القانونية.
Then what are you worried about?
إذن ما الذي يقلقك؟
I found a problem.
لقد وجدت مشكلة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Look at these contracts.
أنظر إلى هذه العقود.
Look at this subcontractor.
انظر إلى هذا المقاول من الباطن.
Is there something wrong with this company?
هل هناك خطأ ما في هذه الشركة؟
I looked into this company.
لقد نظرت في هذه الشركة.
I found out that this company...
لقد اكتشفت أن هذه الشركة...
doesn't actually exist.
لا وجود لها فعليا.
But it received investments...
لكنها حصلت على استثمارات...
from Xuebao and Wanqi at the same time.
من Xuebao و Wanqi في نفس الوقت.
You went to investigate?
ذهبت للتحقيق؟
On your own?
بمفردك؟
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
I see.
أرى.
Chang Ming.
تشانغ مينغ.
I didn't think you'd go this far.
لم أكن أعتقد أنك ستذهب إلى هذا الحد.
What?
ماذا؟
So,
لذا،
this company might just be a shell company.
قد تكون هذه الشركة مجرد شركة وهمية.
They exist just to make money from companies getting listed.
إنهم موجودون فقط لكسب المال من إدراج الشركات.
They take advantage of the merger and acquisition...
إنهم يستغلون عملية الاندماج والاستحواذ...
and make money when the stock price rises.
وكسب المال عندما يرتفع سعر السهم.
Then they'll announce their bankruptcy.
ثم سيعلنون إفلاسهم
Stop it.
اوقفها.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Did you forget what happened to our family?
هل نسيت ما حدث لعائلتنا؟
Did you forget our dad...
هل نسيت والدنا...
No.
لا.
I have to stop this from happening.
يجب أن أمنع حدوث هذا.
If you do that,
إذا فعلت ذلك،
you can never return to Wanqi Group.
لن تتمكن أبدًا من العودة إلى مجموعة وانكي.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But I have to do it.
ولكن يجب علي أن أفعل ذلك.
I've made up my mind.
لقد اتخذت قراري.
But...
لكن...
The press conference is tomorrow.
المؤتمر الصحفي غدا.
I have an idea.
عندي فكرة.
Esteemed leaders and guests,
أيها القادة والضيوف الكرام،
the signing ceremony of Xuebao Group...
حفل توقيع مجموعة Xuebao...
has officially begun.
بدأت رسميا.
Thank you for coming to the signing ceremony.
شكرا لحضوركم حفل التوقيع.
Let's welcome the acting president of Xuebao Group,
دعونا نرحب بالرئيس المؤقت لمجموعة Xuebao،
Mr. Chang Ming, to say a few words.
السيد تشانج مينج، أريد أن أقول بضع كلمات.
First of all, thank you all for coming today.
أولاً، أشكركم جميعًا على حضوركم اليوم.
Working with Wanqi Group...
العمل مع مجموعة وانكي...
is an important boost for Xuebao Group.
يعد هذا دفعة مهمة لمجموعة Xuebao.
From now on, our group will undergo a transformation.
من الآن فصاعدا، سوف تخضع مجموعتنا إلى عملية تحول.
We promise...
نحن نعدك...
to bring better quality products...
لتقديم منتجات ذات جودة أفضل...
with consumer interest in mind.
مع وضع مصلحة المستهلك في الاعتبار.
Let's move on to the interview.
لننتقل إلى المقابلة.
We just received a tip-off.
لقد تلقينا للتو بلاغًا.
It states that the purpose of this merger and acquisition...
وينص على أن الغرض من هذا الدمج والاستحواذ...
is to create a market effect.
هو خلق تأثير السوق.
It does not benefit the two companies...
وهذا لا يصب في مصلحة الشركتين...
but rather, a third-party company called Qimingxing.
بل هي شركة خارجية تدعى Qimingxing.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
The document also includes...
وتتضمن الوثيقة أيضًا...
evidence of the relevant contract.
دليل على العقد ذي الصلة.
Is this all true?
هل كل هذا صحيح؟
Does Qimingxing really exist?
هل تشيمينغشينغ موجودة حقا؟
Or is it just a shell company...
أم أنها مجرد شركة وهمية؟
that makes money from your companies getting listed...
الذي يجني المال من إدراج شركاتك في البورصة...
like the document says?
كما يقول المستند؟
It's a twin contract.
إنه عقد توأم.
I can't believe it.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
I'll go in with you.
سأذهب معك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Trust me. I can handle it.
ثق بي، أنا قادر على التعامل مع الأمر.
Please don't be affected...
من فضلك لا تتأثر...
by this irrelevant information.
من خلال هذه المعلومات غير ذات الصلة.
Please screen these rumors carefully. They are without proof.
يرجى التدقيق في هذه الشائعات بعناية، فهي بلا دليل.
I have proof.
لدي دليل.
I'm a lawyer from Wanqi Group's Legal Department.
أنا محامي من القسم القانوني لمجموعة وانكي.
The contract in my hand can prove it all.
العقد الذي بين يدي يمكن أن يثبت كل ذلك.
As you can see, on page 24 of the contract,
كما ترون في الصفحة 24 من العقد،
this is the result of my investigation on Qimingxing Company.
هذه هي نتيجة تحقيقاتي حول شركة Qimingxing.
Qimingxing Company...
شركة كيمنجكسينج...
is a shell company...
هي شركة وهمية
that doesn't produce anything.
الذي لا ينتج شيئا
The contract you see here...
العقد الذي تراه هنا...
is just an external contract.
هو مجرد عقد خارجي.
What I have in my hand...
ما في يدي...
is the real, internal contract.
هو العقد الداخلي الحقيقي.
Give me a moment.
أعطني لحظة.
I looked into it.
لقد نظرت في الأمر.
You have been in charge of the contract.
لقد كنت مسؤولا عن العقد.
I knew that that day,
لقد عرفت ذلك اليوم،
you were on your way to submit the final contract.
كنت في طريقك لتقديم العقد النهائي.
So I pretended to run into you...
لذلك تظاهرت بأنني التقيت بك...
and had dinner with you.
وتناولت العشاء معك.
I've sent the contents to your phones.
لقد أرسلت المحتويات إلى هواتفكم.
You can check it now.
يمكنك التحقق من ذلك الآن.
- It's a twin contract. - That's right.
- إنه عقد توأم. - هذا صحيح.
Why does she have the internal contract?
لماذا لديها العقد الداخلي؟
I'm sorry, everyone. This is an internal problem.
أنا آسف للجميع. هذه مشكلة داخلية.
I'll take care of it later.
سأعتني بهذا الأمر لاحقًا.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Are you sure the contract you have...
هل أنت متأكد من العقد الذي لديك...
is valid?
هل هو صحيح؟
It's obviously a fake contract...
من الواضح أن هذا عقد مزيف...
that was fabricated to slander the Group.
والتي تم تلفيقها لتشويه سمعة المجموعة.
Everyone, look carefully at the final signature and stamp.
على الجميع أن ينظروا بعناية إلى التوقيع والختم النهائي.
They're all fake.
كلهم مزيفون.
I already knew what you were doing.
لقد عرفت بالفعل ما كنت تفعله.
And I know how you do things.
وأنا أعلم كيف تفعل الأشياء.
Miss.
يفتقد.
If I remember correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح،
you're just a receptionist, right?
أنت مجرد موظفة استقبال، أليس كذلك؟
- She's not an employee? - She's just a receptionist?
- هي ليست موظفة؟ - هي مجرد موظفة استقبال؟
She's just a receptionist.
إنها مجرد موظفة إستقبال.
You seduced...
لقد أغويت...
Mr. Qi of Wanqi Group.
السيد تشى من مجموعة Wanqi.
That's why you had the chance to join the Legal Department.
ولهذا السبب أتيحت لك الفرصة للانضمام إلى القسم القانوني.
Why is she like this?
لماذا هي هكذا؟
That's nonsense.
هذا هراء.
Everything you did...
كل ما فعلته...
- was to frame the group! - That's right.
- كان لتأطير المجموعة! - هذا صحيح.
I didn't expect to have a black sheep like you in our company.
لم أتوقع أن يكون لدينا خروف أسود مثلك في شركتنا.
Go to the HR Department and get your final salary now.
اذهب إلى قسم الموارد البشرية واحصل على راتبك النهائي الآن.
Here, take a picture of this.
هنا، التقط صورة لهذا.
This is the woman who seduced my husband.
هذه هي المرأة التي أغوت زوجي.
Yes, that's right.
نعم هذا صحيح.
She seduced me first.
لقد أغوتني أولاً.
Yes, she seduced me first.
نعم، لقد أغوتني أولاً.
I can't believe you did this...
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنك فعلت هذا...
just to get revenge.
فقط للانتقام.
What kind of person are you?
أي نوع من الأشخاص أنت؟
Is this the kind of person you like?
هل هذا هو نوع الشخص الذي يعجبك؟
Don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
Because you're my brother.
لأنك أخي.
What if I'm not?
ماذا لو لم اكن كذلك؟